Sheridan Gorman was in the spring of life with two of the greatest gifts of
all, time and youth. The time and youth are no match for a bullet, no match for
politicians who prioritize criminals over college freshmen. Sheridan was
shot and killed by someone in our country unlawfully who then committed
other offenses. Why was he allowed to stay? We should ask the political leaders
who put criminal aliens ahead of college girls walking down the street. Why was he
not deported? Why was he allowed to stay here even after additional criminal
allegations? You don't have to ask those who support it. I would not ask the
grieving parents of a dead teenager. They did not make these decisions. They're
just living and dying with the consequences of those decisions. Sheridan's
parents Jessica and Tom Gorman join us. Now I do not have the words to adequately
convey my sympathy to you. Before we talk about her death I really want to
celebrate her life. For both of you, can you tell us about Sheridan? Oh, Sheridan
was extraordinary. She was just like any other American teenager. She was funny,
messy. She was so endearing. We used to joke that she didn't just make friends.
She collected them from every group. I mean whoever she met was a friend and
she deeply valued people. She deeply valued them on every level. She was loyal and
true and she was a teenager. She was not perfect but she was our life. She was
literally our joy. And I imagine she was just like every other 18 year old. She
was not a great driver. She loved animals. She loved her sister. She loved
school. She was an athlete and above all she just loved people. One of the things
I said in our congressional hearing was she had she loved extravagantly and she
did she was not perfect but her heart was nearly perfect. I really believe that.
Tom has anyone given you an answer to the Barthes question of all why? Why was
this defendant accused of murdering your daughter allowed to come into and
remain in this country? We have never received an answer to that tray.
Obviously during the Biden administration the borders were left wide open. A lot
of people coming across were given court appearances but immigration and I
understand 34 percent have failed to appear to those court proceedings. So he
appears to be one of those 34 percent did not show up to his immigration. He did
not have an asylum claim in this country. Made his way to Chicago. He was arrested
for another crime and because of Chicago's sanctuary policies he was left free.
And you know the sanctuary policies they were maybe they were intended to
protect the community. At this time they're not protecting the community. They're
protecting these criminals. When when someone commits a crime and is
apprehended by local police the safest place to for federal agents to do their
job is at the jail during booking or at a courthouse not in the streets but at
those secure locations. Hand them over to federal officials allow them to do their
job and it's no longer a fiscal burden to the state and local communities. And
someone's child lives. It's it's it's just I can't comprehend it. And again you
know New York has doubled down on these sanctuary policies. And the the the
calculus has changed when nearly 20 million unvetted you know immigrants
came across the border. The risks increased. That was an opportunity to
reassess these policies. These policies cannot you know you can't judge a policy
by its intent. You need to judge it based on its outcome. And the outcome is our
dead daughter. Well we're gonna double down on making them live through hearing
this explanation to all those politicians to support open borders in sanctuary
cities. Ms. Gorman I want you to tell them what it is like to hold the cold
lifeless hand of a child for the last time a child killed because of their
policies. Tell them what that feels like. I actually didn't hold her hand. I
couldn't. Tonded. Tonded. There's there is nothing worse than having to go to a
coroner's office and identifying the body of your daughter. There is that it's a
hell that I struggle every day to escape. And we will fight so that no other
parent has to deal with this. This this this is just just another talking point
for a lot of our government officials and even community members. But this is our
life. We have to deal with this every day. What did I do when I held her hand? I
apologize to her. I apologize that the country that she loved failed her. And
I pray to God that I could have been in that body bag instead of her. A hundred
times over would have taken her place. I would have taken anyone's place.
It is indeed a life sentence for both of you. And I I used to do this for a living.
But I can tell you you every one of these cases absolutely breaks your heart
because you see this vibrant life that had so much future ahead of it. And it
is struck down because of nothing in the world that she did. And it infuriates me
and it breaks my heart and it breaks my heart to hear both of you. So I will
continue to be thinking of you. But the most important thing we can do is
create no more parents like you by ending these ridiculous policies. Thank you
for sharing your grief with us. And hopefully it'll motivate the people who
haven't had to hold the hand of a cold, not with us any longer child. God
bless you both. Thank you very much. You too.